Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Jack Girsham, tiger hunter [color photographs], 1958 - 1960s; 4 (Box 1546)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Jack Girsham standing next to a tiger trap], [1.1, 4.2, 4.3, 4.4 on same sheet], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jack Girsham and one other looking for tiger tracks], [1.1, 4.2, 4.3, 4.4 on same sheet], 4
    - [Jack Girsham, a tiger hunter, standing with his shot gun], 5
    - [A caged tiger, caught by Jack Girsham], 6
    - [A tiger roaring, caught by Jack Girsham], 7
    - [A tiger caught by Jack Girsham], 8
  - Subject files: Goldfield, Colorado, undated; 5 (Box 1546)
    - Goldfield, Colo., 1
    - Verso: Goldfield, Colo., 1-verso
  - Subject files: Golf [includes color photographs], circa 1950s - 1970s; 6 (Box 1546)
    - Pete Nakamura - world champ, 1
    - Verso: Pete Nakamura - world champ, 1-verso
    - BOLIVIA: James J. Raaf (Team Captain), Charles "Chick" Evans (Chicago, Illinois, Honorary Chairman of the Francis H. I. Brown International Team Matches), Lowell Thomas and Eduardo Saenz., 2
    - Note: BOLIVIA: James J. Raaf (Team Captain), Charles "Chick" Evans (Chicago, Illinois, Honorary Chairman of the Francis H. I. Brown International Team Matches), Lowell Thomas and Eduardo Saenz., 3
    - with two famous golf pros; Bob Rosburg on LT's right of Palo Alto, Calif. Former P.G.A. champion, Pete Cooper on LT's left - pro for Lawrence Rockefeller at Durado, Puerto Rico; Please credit Bill Mark, Park Sheraton Hotel, N.Y.C., 4
    - Note: with two famous golf pros; Bob Rosburg on LT's right of Palo Alto, Calif. Former P.G.A. champion, Pete Cooper on LT's left - pro for Lawrence Rockefeller at Durado, Puerto Rico; Please credit Bill Mark, Park Sheraton Hotel, N.Y.C., 5
    - Howard Johnson - Howie Johnson and his wife and LT and Bob Feller; Please credit Bill Mark, Park Sheraton Hotel, N.Y.C., 6
    - Verso: Howard Johnson - Howie Johnson and his wife and LT and Bob Feller; Please credit Bill Mark, Park Sheraton Hotel, N.Y.C., 6-verso
    - Caption: The day Ed Bunker broke the course record! [signed] Lowell, 7
    - Verso: Bunker, 7-verso
    - Caption: The day Glenn McHugh broke the course record! [signed] Lowell, 8
    - Verso: McHugh, 8-verso
    - [same group of people as 6.5 & 6.6 unsigned], 9
    - [?], Francis Ouimet and LT, 10
    - Verso: [?], Francis Ouimet and LT, 10-verso
    - LT and Jackie - Golf, 11
    - Verso: LT and Jackie - Golf, 11-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other golfers], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a table with fellow golfers], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas and others on the golf course], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with fellow golfers], 15
    - [A statue in front of a lake on a golf course], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with a statue on the golf course], 17
    - [Golfing friends], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with a statue on the golf course], 19
    - [Man sitting on a statue on the golf course], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas and his friend posing with the can-can statue on the golf course], 21
    - [Golfers eating a picnic lunch on the course], 22
  - Subject files: Mrs. Haruko Goto of Tokyo, 1965; 7 (Box 1546)
    - Lady who waited 7 yrs. To thank me., 1
    - Verso: Lady who waited 7 yrs. To thank me., 1-verso
    - Note: Newspaper clipping concernign Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Haruko Goto and Cinerama [from Asahi Evening News, February 9, 1965 - page 3], 2
    - Note: Newspaper clipping concernign Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Haruko Goto and Cinerama [from Mosnichi(?) News, February 9, 1965], 3
  - Subject files: Greenville, Ohio, 1952; 8 (Box 1546)
    - Note: [from the Journal Herald] Dr. A. F. Sarver, Lowell Thomas, Jelly Burns, and Herman Brown (left to right) chalked their cue sticks yesterday at Burns pool hall as they prepared to resume a game they never finished back in their high school days. Thomas and Dr. Sarver lost Verso: Journal Herald staff photo, Ed Johnsey, 1
    - As a Dayton reporter described it: "L.T. scratched te cue ball in the side pocket whereupon Jelly Burns cleared the table." [4 copies], 2
    - Verso: As a Dayton reporter described it: "L.T. scratched te cue ball in the side pocket whereupon Jelly Burns cleared the table.", 2-verso
    - L.T. engaged in a billiard game in Greenville, Ohio. Seated: Fred Coppock and Mrs. Thomas; return visit, playing pool with old cronies [3 copies], 3
    - Verso: L.T. engaged in a billiard game in Greenville, Ohio. Seated: Fred Coppock and Mrs. Thomas; return visit, playing pool with old cronies, 3-verso
    - LT scratched the cue ball - whereupon Jelly Burns cleared the table!, 4
    - Note: LT scratched the cue ball - whereupon Jelly Burns cleared the table!, 5
    - [L.T. playing pool], 6
    - Note: "Doc" Sarver, LT, Herman Brown, Jelly Burns; Verso: Left to right - Dr. Sarver - Lowell Thomas - Herman Brown and Otto (Jelly) Burns; taken same time as one on wall (in picture collection) [2 copies], 7
    - Verso: Left to right - Dr. Sarver - Lowell Thomas - Herman Brown and Otto (Jelly) Burns; taken same time as one on wall (in picture collection), 7-verso
    - Note: "Doc" Sarver, LT, Herman Brown, Jelly Burns, 8
    - [left to right: Fred Coppock, Mrs. Coppock?, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Lowell Thomas at the Garst Museum] [2 copies], 9
    - [Fred Coppock, the Garst Museum], 10
    - [2 copies] Lowell Thomas visits the Garst Museum in Greenville, Ohio, and presents his "High Mountains" book to Mr. Fred Coppock - accompanied by two young people from Salzburg, Austria, two students, Christl Thalhammer and Roman Pelka, 11
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas visits the Garst Museum in Greenville, Ohio, and presents his "High Mountains" book to Mr. Fred Coppock - accompanied by two young people from Salzburg, Austria, two students, Christl Thalhammer and Roman Pelka, 11-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, second from left, Fred Coppock, third from left], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to Fred Coppock[?] of the Garst Museum], 13
    - Ohio - in museum [Garst Museum?], 14
    - Verso: Ohio - in museum [Garst Museum?], 14-verso
    - Photo by Dan Miley, 15
    - Verso: Photo by Dan Miley, 15-verso
    - [House, 2 copies], 16
  - Subject files: Greenville, Ohio, 1968; 9 (Box 1546)
    - Verso: 61 years later!!!; Left to Right - Leslie Cole, Lowell Thomas and Ray Haber taken Sept. 29, 1968. They played football together at Greenville High School in 1907; Note: For our autobiography file!, 1
    - Verso: 61 years later!!!; Left to Right - Leslie Cole, Lowell Thomas and Ray Haber taken Sept. 29, 1968. They played football together at Greenville High School in 1907, 1-verso
    - Note: For our autobiography file!, 2
    - [Leslie Cole, Lowell Thomas, and Ray Harber], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas signing his book for a little girl], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas signing his book], 5
  - Subject files: Greenville, Ohio (Garst Museum) [color photographs], circa 1970s; 10 (Box 1546)
    - Note: Garst Museum displays, 1
    - [Garst Museum displays], 2
    - [Garst Museum displays], 3
    - [Garst Museum displays], 4
    - [Garst Museum displays], 5
    - [Garst Museum displays], 6
    - [Garst Museum displays], 7
    - M[?] E. Van Kirk, Greenville, Ohio, 8
    - Verso: M[?] E. Van Kirk, Greenville, Ohio, 8-verso
  - Subject files: E. F. Griffiths [color photograph], 1967; 11 (Box 1546)
    - To Lowell from "Griff", 1
    - Verso: To Lowell from "Griff", 1-verso
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from "Griff" (E. F. Griffiths)], 2
  - Subject files: Hammersley Hill, undated; 12 (Box 1546)
    - [Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas], 2
    - Lowell Thomas Quaker Lake 1938, 3
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Quaker Lake 1938, 3-verso
    - [Quaker Lake], 4
    - Hamersley Hill; 2nd home, 5
    - Verso: Hamersley Hill; 2nd home, 5-verso
    - West view of barn [2 copies], 6
    - Verso: West view of barn, 6-verso
    - Southeast view of barn, 7
    - Verso: Southeast view of barn, 7-verso
    - [Tomato plants growing at Hammersley Hill], 8
    - [The barn at Hammersley Hill], 9
    - [Boat on the lake at Hammersley Hill], 10
    - [Boat and dock at Hammersley Hill], 11
    - [The library in Hammersley Hill house], 12
    - [View of the waterfront at Hammersley Hill], 13
    - [The house at Hammersley Hill], 14
    - [Bedroom in Hammersley Hill house], 15
    - [Sitting area in Hammersley Hill house], 16
    - [Fireplace in Hammersley Hill house], 17
    - [Second fireplace in Hammersley Hill house], 18
    - [The back of the Hammersley Hill house], 19
    - [Driveway to Hammersley Hill house], 20
  - Subject files: Hammersley Hill, undated; 13 (Box 1546)
    - [Hammersley Hill house], 1
    - [Backyard party at the Hammersley Hill house], 2
    - [View of the Hammersley Hill house from across the lake], 3
    - [Garage at Hammersley Hill], 4
    - [The Hammersley Hill house], 5
    - [The back of the Hammerlsey Hill house], 6
    - [The lake at Hammersley Hill], 7
    - [The lake at Hammersley Hill], 8
    - [Aerial view of the Hammersley Hill estate], 9
    - [Hammersley Hill], 10
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], 11
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], 12
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], 13
    - [Aerial view of the Hammerlsey Hill house], 14
    - [Aerial view of Hammerlsey Hill], 15
    - [Cars parked by the woods at Hammersley Hill], 16
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], 17
    - [The Hammersley Hill house in winter], 18
    - [The Hammersley Hill house covered in snow], 19
    - [The garage and barn at Hammersley Hill in winter], 20
    - [Tracks left in the snow at Hammersley Hill], 21
    - [Trees in winter at Hammersley Hill], 22
    - [People on the dock at Hammersley Hill], 23
  - Subject files: Hammersley Hill, undated; 14 (Box 1546)
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], [3 copies], 1
    - [Aerial view of the lake at Hammersley Hill], [3 copies], 2
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], [6 copies], 3
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], [3 copies], 4
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], 5
  - Subject files: Hammersley Hill [color photographs], undated; 15 (Box 1546)
    - Note: These have been out of circulation for years. I just discovered them over the weekend. I wonder if they would help in any way?!!, 1
    - [The back of the Hammersley Hill house], 2
    - [The side of the Hammersley Hill house], 3
    - [The Hammerlsey Hill estate], 4
    - [Helicoptor at Hammerlsey Hill], 5
    - [People looking at the helicoptor at Hammerlsey Hills], 6
    - [Person looking inside of the helicoptor at Hammerlsey Hill], 7
    - [Two men looking at the helicoptor at Hammersley Hill], 8
    - [Helicoptor at Hammersley Hill], 9
    - [Second helicoptor at Hammerlsey Hill], 10
    - [Helicoptor taking off at Hammersley Hill], 11
    - [Man boarding helicoptor at Hammersley Hill], 12
    - [The back of the Hammerlsey Hill house], 13
    - [Staircase in the Hammerlsey Hill house], 14
    - [Living room at the Hammerlsey Hill house], 15
    - [Dining room at the Hammerlsey Hill house], 16
    - [Lake in the back of the Hammersley Hill house], 17
    - [Aerial view of Hammerlsey Hill], 18
    - [Aerial view of Hammersley Hill], 19
    - Caption: Fifty years of- THEN, Long ago on that South Sea honeymoon, 20
    - Caption: [(reverse of 15.20) NOW (and all those quiet, placid years), 21
    - [Lake at Hammersley Hill], 22
    - [Waterfront at Hammersley Hill], 23
    - [Entrance to the Hammerlsey Hill house], 24
    - [Back of the Hammersley Hill house], 25
    - [Garden at Hammersley Hill], 26
    - [View of the Hammerlsey Hill house through the trees], 27
  - Subject files: D. Keith Hardy and Lowell Thomas, undated; 16 (Box 1546)
    - Note: L.T. and D.K.H. with Ghurka body-guard at the highest point on the border between Hong Kong and Red China. One British flag and one Chinese border-stone mark the actual boundary. It was from here that the Japanese launched their attack on Hong Kong in 1941. The actual boundary runs down the middle of the valley; Verso: The border - China - Hong Kong, 1
    - Verso: The border - China - Hong Kong, 1-verso
    - Note: L.T. and D.K.H. with Ghurka body-guard at the highest point on the border between Hong Kong and Red China. One British flag and one Chinese border-stone mark the actual boundary. It was from here that the Japanese launched their attack on Hong Kong in 1941. The actual boundary runs down the middle of the valley, 2
    - L.T. and D.K.H. at the boundary sign in the famous village of Sha Tau Kok, which has the Sino-British border running down its main street. One just has to cross the street in order to do a little quiet smuggling! In the background flies China's Communist flag with its five painted stars., 3
    - Note: L.T. and D.K.H. at the boundary sign in the famous village of Sha Tau Kok, which has the Sino-British border running down its main street. One just has to cross the street in order to do a little quiet smuggling! In the background flies China's Communist flag with its five painted stars., 4
    - L.T. and D.K.H. with officers of the British Fourth Hussars - an armored car - reconnaissance unit based on the border. This is D.K.H.'s car which he used as a mobile recording van in Hong Kong. The recording equipment fitted in the back-seat and was driven by the car battery. Nice and cool for the tropics!; Verso: The Fourth Hussars, stationed on the Hong Kong - China border, 5
    - Verso: The Fourth Hussars, stationed on the Hong Kong - China border, 5-verso
    - Note: L.T. and D.K.H. with officers of the British Fourth Hussars - an armored car - reconnaissance unit based on the border. This is D.K.H.'s car which he used as a mobile recording van in Hong Kong. The recording equipment fitted in the back-seat and was driven by the car battery. Nice and cool for the tropics!, 6
  - Subject files: "Devil" Anse Hatfield, undated; 17 (Box 1546)
    - "Devil" Anse Hatfield, 1
    - Verso: "Devil" Anse Hatfield, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Hats, undated; 18 (Box 1546)
    - [Lowell Thomas with many exotic hats], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing a hat], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing an exotic hat], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing a white hat], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas tipping his hat], 5
  - Subject files: John W. Haussermann, circa 1930s; 19 (Box 1546)
    - John W. Haussermann, 1
    - Verso: John W. Haussermann, 1-verso
    - John W. Haussermann, 2
    - Verso: John W. Haussermann, 2-verso
  - Subject files: Hawaiian Debating team and Lowell Thomas, circa 1940; 20 (Box 1546)
    - [Lowell Thomas and the Hawaiian Debating team sitting around a microphone], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and the Hawaiian Debating team talking on the radio], 2
  - Subject files: HAWLT introductions, undated; 21 (Box 1546)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a desk in a studio], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas being recorded in his "office" while he talks about the man in the photograph], 2
  - Subject files: William P. Hayes and Lowell Thomas, circa 1961; 22 (Box 1546)
    - [William P. Hayes and Lowell Thomas], 1
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Bill (William P. Hayes)], [PDF], 2
  - Subject files: Headless Horseman [color photograph], 1962; 23 (Box 1546)
    - [Headless Horseman; men on the golf course], 1
  Box 1547
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Headless Horseman, 1960 - 1962; 1 (Box 1547)
    - Caption: Trude Adams, 1
    - [Woman posing outside], 2
    - [Woman posing on a couch], 3
    - [Portrait of a woman in evening attire], 4
    - Caption: Alan King, 5
    - Caption: Jimmy Joyce, 6
    - Caption: Tina Robin, 7
    - Caption: Memory Lane Quartet, 8
    - Caption: Hibbert, Bird and LaRue, 9
    - [Caption: Hibbert, Bird, and LaRue], 10
    - [Caption: Hibbert, Bird, and LaRue], 11
    - [Man in a tuxedo wearing a turban], 12
    - [Man hitting a golf ball], 13
    - [Four men on the golf course], 14
    - [Men talking to a woman outside], 15
    - [Man standing with a woman on the golf course], 16
    - [Man with girls in marching uniforms], 17
    - [Woman in a meditation pose], 18
    - [Woman in bellydancing (?) dress bending backwards], 19
    - [A woman bellydancing on the golf course], 20
    - [Woman dancing on the golf course for a man], 21
    - [Woman dancing on the golf course], 22
    - [Four men and a woman drinking], 23
  - Subject files: "Heart attack" [includes color photographs], 1963; 2 (Box 1547)
    - [Lowell Thomas with two men], 1
    - Sheldrake 1963, 2
    - Verso: Sheldrake 1963, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men], 3
    - Note: [envelope that likely contained 2.1, 2.2 & 2.3], 4
    - Note: [letter from John A. Gibbons to Lowell Thomas], [PDF], 5
    - [photograph that came with 2.5, letter from John A. Gibbons] Scottish Highland Bull, Sifkalidak Island Alaska, 6
    - Verso: Scottish Highland Bull, Sifkalidak Island Alaska, 6-verso
    - Note: [letter from "Jack" to Frances Ryan Thomas], 7
    - [Photograph that came with 2.7, letter to Frances Ryan Thomas], 8
    - June 22 1963, Lowell Thomas's home Pawling, New York, 9
    - Verso: June 22 1963, Lowell Thomas's home Pawling, New York, 9-verso
    - June 22 1963, Left to right- Patrick Hogan, Joe Kirkwood, Lowell Thomas, Robert Ducas; L. Thomas's home Pawling, New York, 10
    - Verso: June 22 1963, Left to right- Patrick Hogan, Joe Kirkwood, Lowell Thomas, Robert Ducas; L. Thomas's home Pawling, New York, 10-verso
    - [A crowd gathered outside a church], 11
    - Note: [letter with envelope from Richard Rahn, "Joe Kirkwood's occasional assistant" - likely contained photographs 2.9, 2.10 & 2.11], 12
  - Subject files: Paulette Henning and Lowell Thomas [color photograph], 1980 January 25; 3 (Box 1547)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Paulette Henning], 1
    - Verso [Lowell Thomas, Paulette Henning, January 25, 1980], 1-verso
  - Subject files: Theodore Hesburgh, circa 1960s; 4 (Box 1547)
    - Mrs. Frances Thomas, L.T., Father Hesburgh, 1
    - Verso: Mrs. Frances Thomas, L.T., Father Hesburgh, 1-verso
    - [Mrs. Frances Thomas, Lowell Thomas, and Father Hesburgh], 2
    - Sec. of Int. [Secretary of Interior] Rogers Morton, Father Hesburgh, LT, dr. Hobart Van Dusen [Deusen?], William I. Spencer, First National City Bank; Julia: Get name of bank Pres. On right who was chairman of the banquet comm. [committee], 3
    - Verso: Sec. of Int. [Secretary of Interior] Rogers Morton, Father Hesburgh, LT, dr. Hobart Van Dusen [Deusen?], William I. Spencer, First National City Bank; Julia: Get name of bank Pres. On right who was chairman of the banquet comm. [committee], 3-verso
    - L.T.; Father Hesburgh; William I. Spencer, First National City Bank, 4
    - Verso: L.T.; Father Hesburgh; William I. Spencer, First National City Bank, 4-verso
  - Subject files: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas (New Guinea) [includes one color photograph], 1957 November; 5 (Box 1547)
    - HIGHROAD TO ADVENTURE: Native warriors in New Guinea are being instructed by Patrol Officer O'Sullivan of the May River Patrol Post, while two armed members of the New Guinea native police keep guard - a scene which will be presented on TV in the new Lowell Thomas adventure series, 1
    - Note: HIGHROAD TO ADVENTURE: Native warriors in New Guinea are being instructed by Patrol Officer O'Sullivan of the May River Patrol Post, while two armed members of the New Guinea native police keep guard - a scene which will be presented on TV in the new Lowell Thomas adventure series, 2
    - Native warriors in New Guinea, 3
    - HIGHROAD TO ADVENTURE: A flotilla of native canoes leaving Kambaramba Lake village in New Guinea is photographed by a film unit for Lowell Thomas' TV adventure series. The shooting platform on the right consists of two 60-foot canoes lashed catamaran fashion about eight feet apart. A thatched roof covers the platform. The vessel is drawn by an outboard motor, 4
    - Note: HIGHROAD TO ADVENTURE: A flotilla of native canoes leaving Kambaramba Lake village in New Guinea is photographed by a film unit for Lowell Thomas' TV adventure series. The shooting platform on the right consists of two 60-foot canoes lashed catamaran fashion about eight feet apart. A thatched roof covers the platform. The vessel is drawn by an outboard motor, 5
    - THEY PREPARE TO GET AHEAD: Stone Age savages of unexplored Sepik River area in New Guinea prepare for head-hunting battle against a rival tribe and make for a thrilling sequence in the first episode of the new television adventure series, "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which will be shown over the CBS television network on Tuesday, November 12, 8:00 to 9:00 P.M. EST. The series, which will consist of seven full-hour films in color of the adventures of Lowell Thomas and other explorers in such diverse places as New Guinea, the Arctic, Venezuela, the Australian Outback, and African desert and jungle, is being sponsored by the United Motors System and Delco-Remy divisions of General Motors. One film will be shown at specially-scheduled times once a month through May, 6
    - Note: [press release] THEY PREPARE TO GET AHEAD: Stone Age savages of unexplored Sepik River area in New Guinea prepare for head-hunting battle against a rival tribe and make for a thrilling sequence in the first episode of the new television adventure series, "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which will be shown over the CBS television network on Tuesday, November 12, 8:00 to 9:00 P.M. EST. The series, which will consist of seven full-hour films in color of the adventures of Lowell Thomas and other explorers in such diverse places as New Guinea, the Arctic, Venezuela, the Australian Outback, and African desert and jungle, is being sponsored by the United Motors System and Delco-Remy divisions of General Motors. One film will be shown at specially-scheduled times once a month through May, 7
    - Stone Age savages of unexplored Sepik River area, 8
    - SKILL FOR THE KILL; Lowell Thomas watches Stone Age head-hunter in unexplored New Guinea show skill with native bow and arrow during shooting in full color of the first episode in new adventure series, "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which will be shown over CBS television network on Tuesday, November 12, 8:00 to 9:00 P.M. EST. The savage tribesmen, who live exactly as they did 2,000 years ago and have no knowledge of common metals or other contrivances, depend on bow and arrow to kill rival neighbors for souvenir heads. According to the Thomas party, the natives' skill with the bow would make William Tell look like a rank amateur, 9
    - Note: [press release] SKILL FOR THE KILL; Lowell Thomas watches Stone Age head-hunter in unexplored New Guinea show skill with native bow and arrow during shooting in full color of the first episode in new adventure series, "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which will be shown over CBS television network on Tuesday, November 12, 8:00 to 9:00 P.M. EST. The savage tribesmen, who live exactly as they did 2,000 years ago and have no knowledge of common metals or other contrivances, depend on bow and arrow to kill rival neighbors for souvenir heads. According to the Thomas party, the natives' skill with the bow would make William Tell look like a rank amateur, 10
    - Lowell Thomas watches Stone Age head-hunter, 11
    - [11 copies] Lowell Thomas watches Stone Age head-hunter, 12
    - [3 copies] ON DECK FOR ADVENTURE; Lowell Thomas relaxes on river boat taking him and camera crew up the wild Sepik River to photograph Stone Age savages in hitherto unexplored area of New Guinea for first installment of the new television adventure series, "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which will be shown over the CBS television network on Tuesday, November 12, 8:00 to 9:00 P.M. EST, under the sponsorship of the United Motors System and Delco-Remy divisions of General Motors, 13